Hi again and welcome to one of the most
classical and historic cities of Europe
founded as early as 500 years before Christ
located along the Dona River
it was home to many famous historical figures
like Mozart Freud Stalin Brahms and Strauss
We are of course in the second largest
german-speaking city in the world
Vienna let me put on some fitting music
In this city of music the big building
in front of you plays an important role
it's the Grand Opera House and it has
hosted many famous musicians
It can hold over 1,200 guests
at the same time and
as to Vienna people still love their
opera and Viennese balls
it is as popular today as it was in the
19th century
another place who definitely visit
when you're into classical music
is the house where Wolfgang Amadeus
Mozart lived when he was a resident here
he lived in grand style at four large
rooms two small ones
and a spacious kitchen and if we should
believe the stories of him being a party animal
he also had some epic house parties here
not far from here you will find a true
city center that all its nice shops cafes
and restaurants
this road that serviced the center was
once Robin or ditch used by the Roman army
army to defend the city
today is a great place to go shopping
or have lunch
this is the st. Stefan's church and it's
located on stations Platz
it was built in Gothic style in 1147
only to be completed in 1433
can you imagine taking 86 years to
build your house
let some willpower if you want to
have the best view of the city and send
one of these two towers
unfortunately we couldn't as they were
undergoing restoration
located near stephansplatz is this mercy
column showing the Holy Trinity
and nine angels
it was erected after the big play
for Black Death epidemic in 1679 please
spare siding on rats probably causes
bacteria to spread to use killing 76,000
people in the city that was about half
the population of Vienna at the time
now for something brighter if you
want to go
for a nice stroll through Park
Maria today see the plots is definitely
worth a visit
the local residents love to come here
and the national art and history museums
situated near the park
are also main attractions the Natural
History Museum even as a well-preserved
dodo in this collection
one of the best-kept secrets of Vienna
is the st. Peter's Church tucked away on
Peters Platz it might not impress much
from the outside you could easily walk
by it without really noticing it
but it actually is a baroque masterpiece
from the inside yeah take a moment
to take it
all in Vienna had a lot and you're doing
World War 2 under Nazi rule the place
you are standing on once had a bomb
cellar under it in which hundreds of
Austin's were buried alive during a raid
to remind Austrians of the tragedy of
this anti-war and anti-fascist and
monument has been placed here
and here we are at the final destination
of our tour the Hofburg palace
it was the political heart of the Habsburg
Empire it once was the Palace of Empress
Elizabeth better known as
she must have walked along the square in
flamboyant dresses
and with long curly hair ruling her
Empire the legend of her
beauty still prevails and with the
elegant City in mind our tour has come
to an end
I hope you liked historical Vienna as
much as I did till next time
Thank you very much!