welcome to Barcelona the capital city of
Catalonia
and the second most popular city in Spain
this episode will show you
some of the tourist hotspots but more so
some of the popular places for locals to him
right now we're at one of such places
and we'll come back here later to find
out more about this place
first let's head into the city
Nor Amla probably the most famous street
is central Barcelona
this pedestrian streets is lined with
trees on both sides and runs from the
Plaza de Catalunya to Port Phillip
Gamla can be very crowded and it's one of
those streets where you have to be careful
at the northern end of La Habra last is
important Square Plaza de Catalunya
connecting several main streets is
generally considered to leave this city center
the square covers an area of
roughly 50,000 square meters
and is especially known for its
abundance of fountains and statues
parque de la città della is a park on
the northeastern edge of Ciudad Fela for
decades following its creation in the
mid 19th century
this park was the city's only green space
the 70-acre
grounds include the city zoo the palau
del Parliament the Catalunya a small
lake museums and a large fountain
designed by Joseph von sanic here is a
good look on that family which is
commonly known as the cascada meaning
whatever the original structure was
designed by Joseph von Sarah
and his students Antoni gaudí of course
became there's a statue of Venus in a
clamshell
the bark is super tranquil and offers
plenty of spots for an afternoon picnic
or some drinks with friends it's one of
our favorite places to hang out the
Barcelona so we're back at the same
location where we started the bunkers
del Carmel locally just referred to as
bunkers built as an anti-aircraft
fortifications in 1938 during the
Spanish Civil War these days bunkers
offers probably the best view of the city
it's slightly remote location makes it a
bit harder to find for tourists but it's
very popular with locals who come here
in big numbers to drink in the Setting
Sun
obviously we prefer to visit Barcelona
when the weather is great
people here the weather is great pretty
much throughout the year with long
summers and mild winters during summer
the temperatures can easily rise to 90
degrees Fahrenheit so what do you do you
go for a swim
this Mont you extremophile is a great
option to go for refreshing dive the
pool is huge
Andy and the view of city perspective
looking for a more adventurous and
natural place to swim roughly 40
kilometers north of Moscow I stays late
call the doctor
a hidden gem for locals and a favorite
place for dog owners to take the cane
for swim
next to the swimming pool while chewy
Hill offers a couple of other sites
worth seeing him during a castle a
Botanical Garden and the Museum of
Catalunya rocks but sometimes all you
need is a simple bar with a terrace
overlooking the Mediterranean this bar
La Casita
Emilia offers just death
looking for a great Street to experience
some Spanish cuisine tricolor the bligh
better known as the toughest streets of Barcelona
we were particularly enthused
by pictures typical dish from the past
card
Lysanne del Sol which translates a
software as a puzzler
it is the favorite hangout for locals of
possible answers Nastia square is lying
teachers in small bars effects the
marble floor of the plaza heats up in
some nice one
Question on a physical are
which was built as the main entrance go
to 1888 we reverse the face mission
later notice to the expo for the nation
of red brick with a series of freezes
around the ark make
with his last view of the city from the
base of the true
in this episode thank you for watching
together
I hope you had a great done don't forget
to subscribe to our channel and hope to
see you again in one of our next piece