Hi and welcome to another
episode of the gorilla travels
we are in holguin the fourth largest
city in cuba
located in the eastern part of the
island about 500 miles from havana
the city was founded in 1545 by the
spanish officer
son isadoro de hogin
currently we are standing on la loma de
la cruz which gives you an amazing
panoramic view over the city
the climb up this hill consists of 465
stair steps
but as you can see it's definitely worth
Holguin is home to the only organ factory
in cuba
this small factory produces about six
mechanical organs a year
which can be sold between 10 to 25 000
us dollars
the organ music tradition is specific to
the city and an integral part
of the local culture
if you want to experience it firsthand
swing by parque cespedes
on sunday mornings to hear one of the
eight professional organ groups perform
let's swing by now
the official name for this park is
parque carlos manuel de cespedes
but everyone calls it park san jose
named after the church you see here
iglesia de san jose
the park is surrounded by a couple of
art galleries a small museum
and the ministry of culture
the passion and enthusiasm for sports is
ingrained in the cuban culture
from an early age on you can find people
of all ages
playing in parks squares and fields like
you see here
what is the most popular sport in cuba
baseball of course it's the national
sport of cuba
and continues to bind generations and
communities who proudly share in the
traditions and love for the game
nice hit was she safe or out at first
and at this street corner our tour of
hugin has come to an end
we hope you enjoyed it don't forget to
subscribe and see you next time