Welcome to London!
Our tour begins with the London Eye, Europe's
tallest observation wheel.
It is the most famous scenic viewpoint in
the capital with a height of 135 meters.
Starting at Big Ben that is hidden under scaffolding,
we invite you to have a ride on a double-decker
through Westminster Bridge.
This kind of buses is a convenient way to
have a look at the city and its main sights.
Look at the sky: airplanes are leaving colourful trails behind them in honour of the Queen Elizabeth II birthday.
On this bridge, there is always a lot of tourists
and attraction points with the bagpipe among them.
It is one of the most ancient musical instruments
and a national instrument of Scotland.
Tower Bridge is a marvel of engineering.
With a total length of 244 meters, it opens
within a minute.
Even then, pedestrians could cross the river
through a special walkway.
But since 1982, these walkways have been used
as a museum and a viewpoint.
The Tower is one of the most ancient buildings in London.
It is believed to be founded by William I.
For more than a thousand years history, it
had been a fortress, a palace, a treasury,
an armoury, the Royal Mint, a prison and an observatory.
In the 13th century, one of the towers served
as a menagerie with a bear that went fishing
in the Thames.
We are in front of the Westminster Scholars War Memorial
and Westminster Abbey, a beautiful gothic church.
The abbey together with the Palace of Westminster
was designated a UNESCO World Heritage Site
in 1987.
The abbey is a traditional site for the coronation
events and a burial place for the British Monarchs.
Feast your eyes on its courtyard surrounded
by cloister galleries.
Unfortunately, the main premises are prohibited
to be photographed, even with a mobile phone.
In front of us, there is the famous Buckingham Palace.
It was built as a private residence for the Duke.
Afterwards, it was acquired and rebuilt by
King George III
and It became the official residence of
the British Monarchy on the accession of Queen
Victoria only in 1837.
In London, there are many “wild” animals,
such as squirrels, parrots, foxes and deers
that are getting on well in this metropolis.
We were lucky to meet a squirrel in Hyde Park.
In Trafalgar Square, there is the National
Gallery that is among the world’s five most
popular art museums.
One can visit it, like many other London museums,
free of charge.
On top of the 17-meters high Ludgate Hill,
there is St Paul's Cathedral.
It is a fifth Christian church on this site:
one of the previous was destroyed by the Vikings,
others were burnt down in a fire.
The present Cathedral was completed in 1708,
now it is the residence of the Bishop of London.
Now we are in front of Tate Modern, a museum of contemporary art,
and the Millennium Bridge built in honour of the third millennium.
It was also featured in such movies as Harry Potter, Love Actually and Black Mirror TV series.
Just behind HMS Belfast, the World War II-era
cruiser, you can see the highest skyscraper
in the UK, the Shard, rising at 309 meters.
Thank you for this journey made with AirPano!