hi and welcome to another episodes of
immoral travels
We're in varadero a beautiful town situated
in peninsula belong north of cuba
and about the 100 miles east of Havana
Varadero is one of the largest resort areas
in the Caribbean
and is home to some of the most
beautiful beaches in finow
It's a great place someday swim and
simply relax and have a great time.
many famous and Infamous people have
stayed in Varadero
They do including alcohol residents you are
now looking at these days.
It's a restaurant and a bar serving some of the best Mojitos
You'll find anywhere in Cuba
the town is also famous for its old wooden houses
that are still standing strong along its coast line
They were built in the late 19th and early 20th century.
a few hours drive from Varadero live streaming up
the most romantic and pretty city of Cuba
because of its UNESCO world heritage status.
it also is one of the best-preserved
colonial cities in the world.
cobblestone car-free streets give you the feeling
you've traveled back to the 16th century.
one of the most characteristic traits of dreamed up
is the red terracotta tile roofs on the majority of its buildings
How do you like the view from this Bell Tower
the Tower actually is the symbol of the city
most of the sites in cleaning dots are situated around
the main square of the city plaza Mayo variety of musiah
variety of museums and centric images and the historical
and centuries-old buildings and to
the historical atmosphere of the city.
Trinidad  is also a great town to wine and dine
for instance here at a beautiful restaurant La vedavila
you feel right at home with
the life view music and dancers
as you enjoy your delicious meal
to seek your dreams
Rich buttery history of Trinidad
dates back to the 19th century with
the creation of a workshop on
my dino santander
this is the workshop of Sun Santana who's
already learning his trade
through his four-year-old grandson
this way
The family has kept the long-lasting
tradition of modeling clay
the beautiful fired clay objects
can be purchased in his workshop
and here  the tour of
Varadero and Trinidad has come to an end.
We hope you enjoyed it as much as we did. .
Don't forget to subscribe and see you next time
Thank you very much!!!